Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 6: Marketing Files, 49 Boxes (52.75 linear ft.)
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Michel Béroff - California (with Byron Berline):, 1976 -- 1994; 55 folders (Box 190)
    Buchbinder, Rudolf; Bryant, Roger (tenor); Brüggen, Frans; Browning, John, 1933-2003; Caesar, Sid; Bumbry, Grace; Bujones, Fernando; Buechner, Sara Davis; Bronfman, Yefim; Bronstein Barton, Ena; Brown, Les; Band of Renown; Brubeck, Dave; Greer, JoAnn; Bunnell, Jane; Misterii︠a︡ta na bŭlgarskite glasove (Musical group); Bilson, Malcolm; Bilger, David; Blackwell, Harolyn; Black, Neil; Caballé, Montserrat; Bychkov, Semyon; Berline, Byron; California (Musical group); Burchuladze, Paata; Burton, Gary; Burns, Stephen; Boston Camerata; Boston Symphony Chamber Players; Borodin Trio; Kvartet imeni Borodina; Borden, Chris; Borge, Victor; Bonney, Barbara; Bonynge, Richard; Béroff, Michel; Berry, Walter; Blake, Rockwell; Blegen, Judith; Bloom, Claire; Bodner, Phil; Bloch, Boris; Blochwitz, Hans-Peter; Boys of the Lough; Sousa, John Philip, 1854-1932; New Sousa Band; Brion, Keith; Brey, Carter; Brewer, Teresa; Bream, Julian; Stone, Butch; Bolkvadze, Eliso; Morris, Joan; Bolet, Jorge; Bolcom, William; Brandon, Henry (musician); Brandon, David; Brand, Oscar; Braff, Ruby
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Callas Tribute - Régine Crespin:, 1976 -- 1994; 71 folders (Box 191)
    [Folders:] (1) Maria Callas Tribute, 12-11-1983; (2) Calliope; (3) Cab Calloway; (4) Cambridge Buskers; (5) Camerata Academica Salzburg; (6) Camerata Musica Berlin, with Wolf-Dieter Batzdorf; (7) Canadian Brass; (8) Canadian Opera Company; (9) Tito Capobianco; (10) Piero Cappuccilli (didn't appear); (11) Marvellee Cariaga; (12) Judy Carmichael; (13) Pina Carmirelli (see also I Musici); (14) John Carpenter ("The Student Prince"); (15) Scott Carpenter [astronaut]; (16) José Carreras; (17) Benny Carter; (18) Carmen Cavallaro; (19) Cavani String Quartet; (20) Wesley Cease; (21-22) Central Ballet of China; (23) Central Philharmonic of China (Zuohuang Chen, conductor); (24) Renato Cesari; (25) Riccardo Chailly; (26) Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center; (27) Lynn Chang; (28) Carol Channing; (29) Michael Chapdelaine; (30) Ray Charles; (31) Stephanie Chase; (32) Yu Chen; (33) Shura Cherkassky; (34) Chestnut Brass Band; (35) Chicago Symphony Brass; (36) the Chieftains; (37) Alec Chien; (38-40) Chinese Children's Theatre [Chinese Children's Palace of Hangzhou]; (41) Frederic Chiu; (42) Alan Chow; (43) Aldo Ciccolini; (44) Circus Royale; (45) the Clancy Brothers with Robbie O'Connell; (46) Roy Clark; (47) Cleveland Quartet; (48) Ricardo Cobo; (49) Robert Cohen; (50) Charles Colby [William E. Colby]; (51) Coldstream Guards; (52) Jean-Philippe Collard; (53) Buddy Collette; (54) Colorado String Quartet; (55) Betty Comden & Adolph Green; (56) Concertgebouw Orchestra of Amsterdam (Bernard Haitink, conductor); (57) Concord Jazz All-Stars [includes Frank Capp]; (58) Hans Conried; (59) Consortium Antiquum [California-based group with Angene Feves & Charles Perrier]; (60) Barbara Cook; (61) Aaron Copland; (62) Chick Corea Akoustic Band; (63) Franco Corelli; (64) Don Cornell, with Helen O'Connell; (65) Don Cossack Dancers; (66) Mary Costa; (67) Phil Coulter's Pops Orchestra of Ireland; (68) Jean-Philippe Cousteau [Jean-Michel Cousteau?]; (69) Floyd Cramer; (70) Hank Crawford; (71) Régine Crespin.
    Clancy Brothers; O'Connell, Robbie; Chinese Children's Palace of Hangzhou; Chieftains; Chiu, Frederic; Chow, Alan; Ciccolini, Aldo; Circus Royale; Chase, Stephanie; Charles, Ray; Chang, Lynn; Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center; Chien, Alec; Cherkassky, Shura; Chestnut Brass Company (Musical group); Chicago Brass Ensemble; Cambridge Buskers; Chailly, Riccardo; Calloway, Cab; Cesari, Renato; Camerata Academica Salzburg; Cavani Quartet; Camerata Musica-Berlin; National Ballet of China; Capobianco, Tito; Chapdelaine, Michael; Canadian Opera Company; Channing, Carol; Calliope (Musical group); Chen, Zuohuang; Cappuccilli, Piero; Zhong yang yue tuan; Cariaga, Marvellee; Carmichael, Judy; Canadian Brass; Carreras, José; Carpenter, M. Scott (Malcolm Scott); Cavallaro, Carmen; Callas, Maria; Carmirelli, Pina; Carter, Benny; Costa, Mary; Chick Corea Akoustic Band; Crespin, Régine; Crawford, Hank; Coulter, Phil; Cramer, Floyd; Concord All Stars; Feves, Angene; Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990; Capp, Frank; Cornell, Don; O'Connell, Helen; Corea, Chick; Corelli, Franco; Band of the Coldstream Guards (Great Britain); Concertgebouworkest; Haitink, Bernard, 1929-; Colorado Quartet; Collette, Buddy; Cook, Barbara; Conried, Hans; Perrier, Charles; Green, Adolph; Comden, Betty; Collard, Jean Philippe; Cohen, Robert; Cobo, Ricardo; Cleveland Quartet; Clark, Roy; Colby, William Egan
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Bob Crosby - Christoph Eschenbach:, 1976 -- 1994; 68 folders (Box 192)
    [Folders:] (1) Bob Crosby; (2) Gary Crosby; (3) Crystal Palace; (4) Henry Cuesta; (5) Jim Cullum Jazz Band; (6) John Cullum (in "Cyrano de Bergerac"); (7) Czech Chamber Soloists; (8) Georges Cziffra; (9) Clamma Dale; (10) Dancers of Senegal; (11) Eddie Daniels; (12) Mr. Jack Daniel's Original Silver Cornet Band; (13) Danish National Orchestra; (14) Bella Davidovich, with Dmitry Sitkovetsky; (15) Dennis Russell Davies (conductor, Orchester der Beethovenhalle Bonn); (16) Andrew Davis (conductor, Toronto Symphony); (17) Ann Marie De Angelo (Tribute to Pavlova); (18) Joey DeFrancesco; (19) Fernando de la Mora; (20) Alicia de Larrocha; (21) Victoria de los Angeles; (22) Eddie Dean; (23) Eduardo Delgado; (24) Deller Consort (Mark Deller); (25) Del McCoury Band; (26) "The Desert Song" (Romburg); (27) Johnny Desmond; (28) Enrico Di Giuseppe; (29) Andrés Díaz; (30) Mischa and Cipa Dichter; (31) Vic Dickenson; (32) the Dillards; (33) Dimitri; (34) Ghena Dimitrova; (35) Dolmetsch/Schoenfeld Ensemble (Carl Dolmetsch); (36) Plácido Domingo, with Tatiana Troyanos and John DeMain, conductor; (37-38) Plácido Domingo receives the Award for Excellence, 02-01-1992; (39) Sheryn Donahue; (40) Peter Donohoe; (41) Michael Doucet & Beausoleil; (42) Barry Douglas; (43) François Duchâble; (44) Dukes of Dixieland; (45) Arthur Duncan (Stars of Lawrence Welk); (46) Charles Dutoit; (47) George Duvivier; (48) Abba Eban; (49) Bob Eberly; (50) Billy Eckstine; (51) Christiane Edinger; (52) Ryan Edwards; (53) Youri Egorov; (54) Larry Elgart, with orchestra; (55) Duke Ellington tribute, "Mostly Duke," with John and Donald Mills, Herb Jeffries, Barbara McNair, Gene Bell; (56) Bill Elliott Swing Orchestra; (57) Emerson String Quartet; (58) Empire Brass; (59) Endellion String Quartet; (60) Alison England; (61) English Baroque Soloists; (62) English Chamber Orchestra, with Jeffrey Tate; (63) English Concert, with Trevor Pinnock; (64) Ensemble for Early Music (Frederick Renz, director; "Daniel and the Lions"); (65) Ensemble Project Ars Nova; (66) Ensemble Vienna-Berlin; (67) Kaaren Erickson; (68) Christoph Eschenbach.
    Ensemble Wien-Berlin; Dickenson, Vic; Desmond, Johnny; Eschenbach, Christoph; Di Giuseppe, Enrico; Erickson, Kaaren; Diaz, Andrés; Dichter, Cipa; Dichter, Misha, 1945-; Del McCoury Band; Deller, Mark; Deller Consort; Delgado, Eduardo (pianist); McCoury, Del; Larrocha, Alicia de; Angeles, Victoria de los; Dean, Eddie (vocalist); De Angelo, Ann Marie; DeFrancesco, Joey; McNair, Barbara; Davies, Dennis Russell; Mills, Donald; Mora, Fernando de la; Mills Brothers; Sitkovetsky, Dmitry; Bill Elliott Swing Orchestra; Davis, Andrew; English Baroque Soloists; Mr. Jack Daniel’s Original Silver Cornet Band; Ellington, Duke; Statsradiofoniens symfoniorkester (Copenhagen, Denmark); Bell, Gene; Davidovich, Bella; Jeffries, Herb; Daniels, Eddie; Pinnock, Trevor; National Dance Company of Senegal; Ensemble for Early Music; Dale, Clamma; Endellion String Quartet; Cziffra, Georges; England, Alison; Čeští komorní sólisté; Renz, Frederick; Crosby, Bob; English Chamber Orchestra; Cullum, Jim; Tate, Jeffrey; Cuesta, Henry; English Concert (Musical group); Crosby, Gary; Empire Brass (Musical group); Ensemble Project Ars Nova; Elliott, Bill (conductor); Emerson String Quartet; Edinger, Christiane; Edwards, Ryan; Elgart, Larry; Cullum, John; Egorov, Youri; Jim Cullum Jazz Band; Eberly, Bob; Dukes of Dixieland; Eckstine, Billy; Eban, Abba Solomon; Duvivier, George; Duchâble, François; Duncan, Arthur; Dutoit, Charles; Beausoleil (Musical group); Donahue, Sheryn, soprano; Doucet, Michael; Douglas, Barry; Troyanos, Tatiana; DeMain, John; Domingo, Plácido; Donohoe, Peter; Dolmetsch, Carl F.; Dimitrova, Gena Macheva; Dimitri; Dillards; Saxby, Joseph, 1910-1997; Schoenfeld, Eleanore; Schoenfeld, Alice; Dolmetsch-Schoenfeld Ensemble
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Eroica Trio - Evelyn Glennie:, 1974 -- 1994; 65 folders (Box 193)
    [Folders:] (1) Eroica Trio; (2) Alfred Eschwé; (3) Faith Esham; (4) Joseph Evans; (5) Fairfield Four; (6) Eileen Farrell; (7) Suzanne Farrell (see also American Ballet); (8) Giora Feidman; (9) Eliot Feld Ballet; (10) Vladimir Feltsman; (11) Maynard Ferguson; (12) Eduardo Fernández; (13) Festival of the Nile; (14) Janina Fialkowska; (15) Fidelio String Quartet; (16) 15th Air Force Band of the Golden West; (17) Fifty Fingers (Roger Kellaway [replacement for Kenny Barron], Alan Broadbent, Dick Hyman, Gerald Wiggins); (18) Rudolf Firkusny; (19) Annie Fischer; (20) Eliot Fisk; (21) Ella Fitzgerald; (22) Fitzwilliam String Quartet; (23) Five Blind Boys of Alabama; (24) Michael Flatley; (25) Myron Florin; (26) Eugene Fodor; (27) Helen Forrest; (28) Gary Foster; (29) Ian Fountain; (30) Four Aces (with Al Alberts); (31) Four Freshmen; (32) (New) Four Preps; (33) Virgil Fox; (34) Panama Francis; (35) Clay Francisco; (36) Pamela Frank; (37) Nnenna Freelon; (38) Mirella Freni; (39) Semyon Fridman; (40) Milton Friedman; (41) Benjamin Frith; (42) Frula; (43) Leo Fuchs; (44) Cecilia Fusco; (45) Zehava Gal; (46) Geri Galian; (47) Thomas Gallant; (48-49) James Galway (with Kazuhito Yamashita); (50) John Eliot Gardiner; (51) John Gary; (52) Gathering of the Clans; (53) Giorgio Gatti (Elvira Spica and Ernesto Palacio); (54) Paul Gaulin Mime Company; (55) Andrei Gavrilov; (56) Crystal Gayle; (57) Georgian Chamber Orchestra; (58) Gewandhaus Orchestra of Leipzig with Kurt Masur; (59) Nicolai Ghiaurov; (60) Edoardo Giménez; (61) Bronislaw Gimpel; (62) Jakob Gimpel; (63) Carlo Maria Giulini (see also Vienna Symphony); (64) Glendale Symphony Orchestra; (65) Evelyn Glennie.
    Esham, Faith; Georgisches Kammerorchester; Gavrilov, Andrei; Gatti, Giorgio; Paul Gaulin Mime Company; Palacio, Ernesto; Spica, Elvira; Masur, Kurt; Ghiaurov, Nicolai; Ferguson, Maynard; Frith, Benjamin; Feltsman, Vladimir; Fridman, Semyon; Feld, Eliot; Gal, Zehava; Feld Ballet; Gary, John; Farrell, Eileen, 1920-2002; Galway, James; Eschwé, Alfred; Gallant, Thomas (oboist); Eroica Trio; Yamashita, Kazuhito; Evans, Joseph; Gardiner, John Eliot; Giménez, Eduardo; Gewandhausorchester Leipzig; Gayle, Crystal; Glennie, Evelyn; Glendale Symphony Orchestra; Giulini, Carlo Maria; Gimpel, Bronislav; Gimpel, Jakob; Fernández, Eduardo; Fischer, Annie; Fisk, Eliot; Fitzgerald, Ella; Fitzwilliam String Quartet; Foster, Gary; Fountain, Ian; Wiggins, Gerald; Firkušný, Rudolf; Broadbent, Alan; Hyman, Dick; Farrell, Suzanne; Feidman, Giora; Five Blind Boys of Alabama; Fialkowska, Janina; Fidelio Quartet; Kellaway, Roger; Frank, Pamela; Francis, Panama; Freni, Mirella; Francisco, Clay; Galian, Geri; Fuchs, Leo; Friedman, Milton; Fusco, Cecilia; Floren, Myron; Flatley, Michael; Fodor, Eugene; Forrest, Helen; Four Freshmen (Musical group); Freelon, Nnenna; Fox, Virgil; Fairfield Four
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Mona Golabek - Mariette Hartley:, 1976 -- 1995; 55 folders (Box 194)
    [Folders:] (1) Mona Golabek; (2) Gold Rush Cornet Band; (3) Juliana Gondek; (4) Richard Goode; (5) Benny Goodman; (6) Galina Gorchakova (with Sergeĭ Leĭferkus); (7) Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus; (8) Gary Graffman; (9) Martha Graham Company; (10) Les Grands Ballets Canadiens; (11) Gogi Grant; (12) Stéphane Grappelli; (13) Patrick Graybill (National Theatre of the Deaf); (14) Joe Graydon; (15) the Great Guitars (Charlie Byrd, Barney Kessel, Bucky Pizzarelli); (16) Buddy Greco; (17-18) José Greco Company; (19) Greek Dancers (Dora Stratou); (20) Jo Ann Greer; (21) David Grisman; (22) Edita Gruberova; (23) Guarneri Quartet; (24) John Guarnieri; (25) Isabelle Guérin; (26-27) Guitar Summit (Joe Pass, Paco Péña, Leo Kottke, Pepe Romero); (28) Michael Gurt; (29) Horacio Gutiérrez; (30) Karl Haas; (31) Charlie Haden (Quartet West); (32) Jerry Hadley; (33) Hagegård, Håkan (performing with Barbara Bonney and Judith Blegen, separately); (34) Merle Haggard; (35) Connie Haines; (36) Bernard Haitink (see also Concertgebouw Orchestra of Amsterdam); (37) William Hall/William Hall Chorale; (38) Carl Halvorson; (39) Leonid Hambro/Hambro Piano Quartet; (40) Marc-André Hamelin; (41) Scott Hamilton; (42) Marvin Hamlisch; (43) Thomas Hampson; (44) Lionel Hampton; (45) Lars Hannibal (see Michala Petri/Lars Hannibal); (46) Hanover Band; (47) Roy Hargrove; (48) Ofra Harnoy; (49) Lynn Harrell; (50) Brenda Harris; (51-52) Emmylou Harris; (53) John Hartford (with California (group), featuring Byron Berline); (54) Sidney Harth; (55) Mariette Hartley.
    Goodman, Benny; Goode, Richard; Gondek, Juliana; Golabek, Mona; Leĭferkus, Sergeĭ; Gorchakova, Galina; Graydon, Joe; Harrell, Lynn; Harnoy, Ofra; Hanover Band; Hannibal, Lars; Hartley, Mariette; Hartford, John; Harris, Emmylou; Harris, Brenda (soprano); Pizzarelli, Bucky; Greco, Buddy; Byrd, Charlie; Kessel, Barney; Greer, JoAnn; Guérin, Isabelle; Gruberova, Edita; Grisman, David; Grant, Gogi; Grappelli, Stéphane; Graffman, Gary; Grands ballets canadiens; Martha Graham Dance Company; Lotte Goslar’s Pantomime Circus; José Greco Company; Graybill, Patrick; Hampson, Thomas; Hamlisch, Marvin; Pass, Joe; Hampton, Lionel; Hadley, Jerry; Quartet West; Haas, Karl; Haden, Charlie; Guarnieri, John; Gutiérrez, Horacio; Hargrove, Roy; Guarneri Quartet; Péña, Paco; Kottke, Leo; Gurt, Michael; Romero, Pepe; Hamelin, Marc-André; Hambro, Leonid; Hambro Piano Quartet; William Hall Chorale; Berline, Byron; California (Musical group); Harth, Sidney; Hamilton, Scott; Haggard, Merle; Hagegård, Håkan; Bonney, Barbara; Blegen, Judith; Halvorson, Carl; Hall, William Dawson; Haitink, Bernard, 1929-; Haines, Connie
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Michael Kieran Harvey - Juilliard String Quartet:, 1976 -- 1995; 66 folders (Box 195)
    [Folders:] (1) Michael Kieran Harvey (see also Pogorelich Competition); (2) Buddy Hatton; (3) Hayastan Dance Ensemble; (4) Horace Heidt, Jr.; (5) Jon Hendricks; (6) Harold Hensley; (7) Woody Herman, with Richard Stoltzman; (8) Hilliard Ensemble; (9) Al Hirt with band; (10) Gary Hoffman; (11) Hoffnung Festival; (12) Christopher Hogwood (see also Academy of Ancient Music); (13) Hal Holbrook (as Mark Twain); (14) Heinz Holliger; (15) John Holod; (16) Ben Holt; (17) Marilyn Horne; (18-20) Vladimir Horowitz; (21) Hot Frogs Jumping Jazz Band; (22) Stephen Hough; (23) Houston Ballet; (24) Ray Howard; (25) Freddie Hubbard; (26) Eddie Hubble; (27) Hungarian State Folk Ensemble; (28) Bobby Hutcherson; (29) Jorma Hynninen; (30) I Cantori; (31-32) I Musici; (33) I Solisti di Zagreb; (34) Keith Ikaia-Purdy; (35) Imedi Youth Dance Ensemble; (36) Ink Spots (Johnny Smith & the New Ink Spots); (37) Irish Rovers; (38) Israel Ballet; (39) Israel Chamber Orchestra (with Shlomo Mintz, Yoav Talmi); (40) Israel Piano Trio; (41) Eugene Istomin; (42) Jose Iturbi; (43) Burl Ives; (44) Roman Jabłoński; (45) Oliver Jackson; (46) Derek Jacobi; (47) Claudio Jaffe; (48) Harry James; (49) Lance James (Oakland Ballet); (50) Antonio Janigro (see also I Solisti di Zagreb); (51) Fran Jeffries; (52) Herb Jeffries; (53) Jai Jeffryes; (54) David Jennings; (55) Jim and Jesse [McReynolds] (with Ralph Stanley); (56) Emma Johnson; (57) Johnson Mountain Boys; (58) Doug Jones; (59) Jack Jones; (60) Philip Jones [Brass Ensemble]; (61) Shirley Jones; (62) Tedd Joselson; (63) Charles Jude; (64) Chantal Juillet; (65-66) Juilliard String Quartet (see also Charles Neidich).
    Philip Jones Brass Ensemble; Hendricks, Jon; Joselson, Tedd; Hogwood, Christopher; Jones, Jack; Hoffnung, Gerard; Jones, Shirley; Hoffman, Gary; Juilliard String Quartet; Hatton, Buddy; Jones, Doug; Harvey, Michael Kieran; Jude, Charles; Herman, Woody; Juillet, Chantal; Hensley, Harold; Hubble, Ed; Horne, Marilyn; Magyar Állami Népi Együttes; Hynninen, Jorma; Hough, Stephen; Houston Ballet; Horowitz, Vladimir; Hot Frogs (Musical group); Holbrook, Hal; Holod, John; Hubbard, Freddie; Holliger, Heinz; Hilliard Ensemble; Hirt, Al; Holt, Ben; Stoltzman, Richard; Ives, Burl; Jabłoński, Roman; Irish Rovers (Musical group); New Ink Spots (Musical group); Israel Chamber Orchestra; Israel Ballet; Mintz, Shlomo; Israel Piano Trio; Istomin, Eugene; Talmi, Yoav; Cantori; Iturbi, Jose; Zagrebački solisti; Musici; Hutcherson, Bobby; Ikaia-Purdy, Keith; McReynolds, Jesse; McReynolds, Jim; Stanley, Ralph; Jim and Jesse; Johnson Mountain Boys; Johnson, Emma; Jeffryes, Jai; Jeffries, Herb; Jeffries, Fran; Janigro, Antonio; Pittman-Jennings, David; James, Lance; Jaffe, Claudio; James, Harry; Jackson, Oliver; Jacobi, Derek
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Jury's Irish Cabaret of Dublin - Los Angeles Ballet:, 1975 -- 1995; 78 folders (Box 196)
    [Folders:] (1) Jury's Irish Cabaret of Dublin; (2) Jeffrey Kahane; (3) Kalichstein-Laredo-Robinson Trio; (4) Turan-Mirza Kamal; (5) Richard Kapp; (6) Flying Karamazov Brothers; (7) Karpatok; (8) Ida Kavafian; (9) Leonidas Kavakos; (10) Stan Kenton Band [Big Sandy]; (11) Yong Uck Kim; (12) the Four King Sisters; (13) Kings of Swing (Terry Gibbs, Buddy De Franco, Larry Koonse); (14-15) the King's Singers; (16) the Kingston Trio; (17) Gelsey Kirkland and Johnna Kirkland; (18) Klezmer Conservatory Band; (19) the Klezmorim; (20) Walter Klien; (21) Sherry Kloss; (22) Kenʼichirō Kobayashi; (23) Zoltán Kocsis; (24) Alfons and Aloys Kontarsky; (25) Murray Korda and His Monseigneur Strings; (26) Koslov Youth Dance Ensemble; (27) Stephen Bishop-Kovacevich; (28) Krasnayarsk; (29) Alfredo Kraus; (30) Alison Krauss and Union Station; (31) Gidon Kremer; (32) Anton Kuerti; (33) Valery Kuleshov; (34) Kunakova Ballet; (35) LAADA/CADC [Los Angeles Area Dance Alliance/California Association of Dance Companies] Benefit, 05-03-1978; (36) Katia and Marielle Labèque; (37) Alexandre Lagoya; (38) Cleo Laine/John Dankworth Quartet; (39) Frankie Laine; (40) Gary Lakes; (41) Nancy LaMott; (42) Lamplighters (in Gilbert and Sullivan's "Patience"); (43) "Land of Smiles" by Franz Lehar [Viennese Operatta Co. of New York], Robert Van Valkenburg; (44) Marie-Pierre Langlamet; (45) Sylvia Lanka; (46) Ed Lark; (47) Douglas Lawrence; (48) Hubert Laws; (49) Evelyn Lear and Thomas Stewart; (50) Michel Legrand; (51) Manuel Legris; (52) David Leisner; (53) James Levine (see also Vienna Philharmonic); (54) Daniel Lewis (USC Symphony Orchestra); (55) Laurie Lewis, with Del McCoury/Del McCoury Band; (56) Ramsey Lewis (see also Billy Taylor); (57) Bella Lewitzky Dancers; (58) Cecile Licad; (59) Life Member Orchestra (also Senior Symphony) AFM, Local 47; (60) the Limeliters; (61) Cho-Liang Lin; (62) Samuel Lipman; (63) Little Eagles of Siberia; (64) Andrew Litton; (65) Guy Lombardo/Al Pierson; (66) London Brass; (67) London Early Music Group; (68) George London; (69) London Philharmonic Orchestra (with Klaus Tennstedt); (70) London Players Theatre [London Follies]; (71) Jesús López Cobos (Cincinnati Symphony); (72) Jorge López-Yañez; (73) Thomas Lorango; (74) Pilar Lorengar; (75) Louis Lortie; (76-78) Los Angeles Ballet (includes "Cinderella" and other productions).
    Lewis, Daniel; Lewis, Laurie; Leisner, David; Levine, James; McCoury, Del; Lewis, Ramsey; USC Symphony Orchestra; Del McCoury Band; London Philharmonic Orchestra; Kamal, Turan-Mirza (guitarist); Limeliters (Musical group); Kapp, Richard; London Brass (Musical group); Kahane, Jeffrey; London Early Music Group; Kalichstein-Laredo-Robinson Trio; Litton, Andrew; Robinson, Sharon; Licad, Cecile; Jury's Irish Cabaret; Lin, Cho-Liang; Kalichstein, Joseph; Lipman, Samuel; Laredo, Jaime; Flying Karamazov Brothers; Lortie, Louis; Kavafian, Ida; Lorengar, Pilar; Kavakos, Leonidas; Murray Korda and His Monseigneur Strings; Lorango, Thomas; Stan Kenton Orchestra; Cobos, Jesús López; Koonse, Larry; Pierson, Al; Gibbs, Terry; Lombardo, Guy; King’s Singers (Vocal group); London, George; Kingston Trio; Tennstedt, Klaus; King Sisters; Kim, Young Uck; De Franco, Buddy; Kirkland, Gelsey; López-Yañez, Jorge; Kirkland, Johnna; Klezmorim; Klezmer Conservatory Band; Kontarsky, Aloys; Klien, Walter; Kobayashi, Kenʼichirō; Kocsis, Zoltán; Kontarsky, Alfons; Union Station (Musical group); Kremer, Gidon; Koslov Youth Dance Ensemble of Moscow; Kloss, Sherry; Kuleshov, Valery; Kovacevich, Stephen; Kraus, Alfredo; Krauss, Alison; Laine, Frankie; Lakes, Gary; Dankworth, John; Kuerti, Anton; Labèque, Marielle; Labèque, Katia; Laine, Cleo; Lagoya, Alexandre; LaMott, Nancy; Viennese Operetta Company of New York; Langlamet, Marie-Pierre; Lamplighters (Operetta company); Lawrence, Douglas; Legris, Manuel; Lark, Ed; Laws, Hubert; Legrand, Michel; Bella Lewitzky Dance Company; Lear, Evelyn; Stewart, Thomas
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra - Alicia Markova:, 1975 -- 1994; 32 folders (Box 197)
    [Folders:] (1-5) Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra (L.A.C.O.); (6) Los Angeles Guitar Quartet (John Dearman, William Kanengiser, Scott Tennant, Andrew York); (7) Los Angeles Master Chorale/Roger Wagner; (8) Los Angeles Piano Quartet; (9) Los Angeles Vocal Arts Ensemble; (10) Patty Loveless; (11) Norman Luboff/Norman Luboff Choir; (12) Andrea Lucchesini; (13) Lorna Luft; (14) Benedetto Lupo; (15) Dame Moura Lympany; (16) Panayis Lyras; (17) Yo-Yo Ma; (18) George Malcolm; (19) Catherine Malfitano; (20) Henry Mancini; (21) Manhattan Tap (Diane Walker and Buster Brown); (22) Herbie Mann with Jasil Brazz Quartet; (23) George P. Mansour, Jr.; (24) Alessandra Marc; (25-28) Marcel Marceau; (29) Marine Band [U.S.M.C.]; (30) Alʹbert Markov; (31) Alexander Markov; (32) Alicia Markova and Anton Dolin.
    Norman Luboff Choir; Luboff, Norman; Loveless, Patty; Lucchesini, Andrea; Lupo, Benedetto; Dearman, John; Wagner, Roger; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Mann, Herbie; Lympany, Moura; Lyras, Panayis; Ma, Yo-Yo; Marceau, Marcel; Malcolm, George, 1917-1997; Malfitano, Catherine; Luft, Lorna; Markov, Alʹbert; United States Marine Band; Markova, Alicia, Dame; Markov, Alexander; Marc, Alessandra; Dolin, Anton; Mancini, Henry; Brown, Buster; L.A. Guitar Quartet; Los Angeles Vocal Arts Ensemble; Los Angeles Piano Quartet; Los Angeles Master Chorale; Tennant, Scott; Kanengiser, William; York, Andrew
  - Alphabetical Photograph Files: Alicia Markova - Musicians of Swanne Alley:, 1975 -- 1995; 69 folders (Box 198)